

# **CONTACT INFORMATION:**

+38-050-78-325-78

Ivaschenko\_u@ukr.net

https://github.com/Yuriilva

llinkedin.com/in/yurii-ivashchenko

Ukraine, Kyiv

## **TECH SKILLS**

HTML5/CSS3/SASS
GIT
JavaScript
React
Redux
Redux Toolkit
Node.js
MongoDB
Mongoose
Webpack

Parcel
REST API
Netrify
SKILLS

Experience working in a team Positive Autonomous Attentive

# LANGUAGE SKILLS

English (intermediate) Ukrainian (Native) Russian (Native)

# Yurii Ivashchenko

# **Full Stack Developer**

# **SUMMARY**

I am a Full Stack Developer!
I love my life and love what I do.

I have knowledge of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React and Node.js. Also, I have hands-on experience in following Agile /Scrum methodology when was working in a team. I am a fast learner, responsible, and ready for challenging tasks.

## **PROJECT EXPERIENCE:**

#### PROJECT PRO TEST:

https://github.com/AnnaSobchenko/pro-test

Technologies: JS, HTML5/CSS3/SASS, Parcel, Git About project: My role in this project was developer!

#### **Project name Kapusta:**

https://github.com/YelyzavetaLukianova/Money-project-react.git

Technologies: React, Redux, JS, HTML5/CSS, Swagger backend, libraries About project: My role in this project was developer!

#### Project name Filmoteka:

https://yuriiiva.github.io/cinema-library-11-21/

Technologies: JS, HTML5/CSS3/SASS, Parcel, REST API About project: My role in this project was Team leader!

# Project name Snake:

https://github.com/Yuriilva/snake-game-2.git

Technologies: JS, HTML5/CSS3/SASS, Parcel, Git About project: My role in this project was scrum master!

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**VICIUNAI 2019-2021** 

Head of sales department:

- -managed a division in Kyiv(10 people),
- -territory development strategy,
- -team training.
- -sfles

# Anheuser-Busch InBev 2009-2017

**Supervisor:** 

- -I had a team(12 people) in Sumy first and then in Kyiv(8 people)
- -territory development strategy,
- -team training,
- -seles

# **EDUCATION**

Sumy State University 2003-2005: speciality -Electronic

#### Courses

- GoIT Academy Bootcamp 2021: Full Stack Developer